<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CradleRide Logger</string>

    <string name="button_Initialise">Initialise GPS</string>
    <string name="button_Start">Start Recording</string>
    <string name="button_Stop">Stop Recording</string>

    <string name="button_Pothole">Pothole</string>
    <string name="button_SurfaceBad">Bad Surface</string>
    <string name="button_SurfaceGood">Good Surface</string>

    <string name="startGPS">Please start the GPS receiver.</string>
    <string name="initialising">Please wait for the GPS to fix your location.</string>
    <string name="locked">The GPS is locked. Please start recording your journey.</string>
    <string name="recording">Please turn your screen off for the duration of the journey.</string>
    <string name="finished">Thank you for recording your journey.</string>
    <string name="crashed">Something went wrong with recording. Please restart the app.</string>
    <string name="permissions">Please grant all permissions to enable recording.</string>

    <string name="info_display">\nPlease place the phone with the right side facing forward travel.\n --->\n </string>

    <string name="ad_title">Disclosure Agreement</string>
    <string name="ad_button">Accept</string>
    <string name="ad_checkbox">I confirm I have read the agreement.</string>

    <string name="disclosure">This is where the disclosure agreement will go once the wording has been finalised.
        \n\nUnless the user scrolls to the bottom of the agreement and ticks the box, the \'accept\' button is disabled.
        \n\nFor all new users, the disclosure agreement will appear when they first start the app - before any sensors have been
        identified and before their Unique ID is assigned.
        \n\nIn the same way the Unique ID only gets set once, the disclosure agreement will not show after the first time starting
        the app (unless the user declines to accept, in which case they won\'t get past the agreement no matter how many times they
        restart the app.
        \n\n\nWhile I have looked at the Google Play guidelines and also read through the privacy policy you wrote, I am unsure what to
        put in the final agreement as I haven\'t dealt with them before.
        \n\n\nAs you can probably tell, I am waffling.
        \n\n\nThis is to allow you to see how the user needs to scroll down before being able to progress.
        \n\nTry the \'back\' button if you wish. . .
        \n\nAny luck? The answer should be no.
        \n\nWhile there is no way of ensuring users actually READ the agreement, this makes it slightly more likely!
        \n\nAnd now you can check the box and accept the agreement.
        \n</string>

</resources>
