<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CradleRide Logger</string>

    <string name="id_string">Unique ID: \t</string>
    <string name="version_string">\nVersion: \t</string>
    <string name="instruct_placeholder">Instructions</string>

    <string name="butt_init">Searching for GPS</string>
    <string name="butt_start">Start Recording</string>
    <string name="butt_stop">Stop Recording</string>

    <string name="startGPS">Please start the recording and place your phone in position.</string>
    <string name="failed">GPS failed to lock on. \n\nPlease try again.</string>
    <string name="initialising">Once GPS is locked, recording will start automatically.</string>
    <string name="recording">Please do not touch your phone during the journey.</string>
    <string name="finished">Thank you for recording your journey.</string>
    <string name="crashed">Something went wrong with recording. \n\nPlease restart the app.</string>
    <string name="permissions">Please grant all permissions to enable recording.</string>

    <string name="orient_info">Align arrow with forward travel.\n\n ---> </string>

    <string name="ad_title">Disclosure Agreement</string>
    <string name="ad_button">Accept</string>
    <string name="ad_checkbox">I consent to my data being used for the purposes of research.</string>

    <string name="disclosure">This app collects GPS, accelerometer, gyroscope, magnetometer and peak audio data from the
        phone when the app is running and the user has requested logging be started.
        \n\nThe data collected is sent securely to our server for analysis and use in a research project.
    </string>

    <string name="butt_ok">@android:string/ok</string>
    <string name="butt_cancel">@android:string/cancel</string>

    <string name="menu_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_title">CradleRide Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy"><b>Data collection</b>
        \n\nThe CradleRide logger app is a research tool for collecting sensor data from phones. The sensor data is not collected
        automatically. It will only start with direct user intervention.

        \n\nThe data collected depends on the features available on the phone being used, but can include:
        \n\tAccelerometer data, sampled at the fastest rate
        \n\tGyroscope data, sampled at the fastest rate
        \n\tGPS position data, sampled at approximately 1Hz
        \n\tAudio data, sampled at 100-200Hz - the highest amplitude component within the sampling time window only

        \n\nA unique identifier is used per phone, so that multiple uses of the same phone can be correlated and combined.

        \n\nAll data is saved on the phone locally, then after the user stops the logging session and the phone subsequently
        enters a WiFi zone, the saved data is uploaded to our servers only.

        \n\nThe data saved on our server will not be shared with any third party without further consultation with the users.

        \n\nThe data from multiple logging events from the same user will be combined to produce aggregate data about the
        environment in which the user is located, but not about the user themselves.

        \n\nAll data is transmitted securely.\n</string>

    <string name="as_menu">Auto-Stop</string>
    <string name="as_check_title">Turning Auto-Stop Off</string>
    <string name="as_check_message">Auto-stop shuts off the app when accidentally left logging.
        \n\nTurning off could lead to excess battery usage.</string>
    <string name="as_on">Auto-Stop enabled</string>
    <string name="as_off">Auto-Stop disabled</string>

    <string name="menu_delay">Start Delay: \t</string>
    <string name="menu_timeout">GPS Timeout: \t</string>
    <string name="menu_seconds">\t seconds.</string>
    <string name="menu_testing">Testing (no GPS)</string>
    <string name="menu_test_init">Initialise before test.</string>

    <string name="test_on">Testing on. GPS disabled.</string>
    <string name="test_off">Testing off. GPS enabled.</string>
    <string name="test_init_on">Initialising on.</string>
    <string name="test_init_off">Initialising off.</string>

    <string name="recording_data">Journey being recorded. Please do not move the phone.</string>

</resources>
